<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Three Buttons</string>
    <string name="text_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="text_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="text_one">Text One</string>

    <string name="passage_one">Android Studio is the official[7] integrated development environment (IDE) for Google\'s Android operating system, built on JetBrains\' IntelliJ IDEA software and designed specifically for Android development.[8] It is available for download on Windows, macOS and Linux based operating systems.[9][10] It is a replacement for the Eclipse Android Development Tools (ADT) as the primary IDE for native Android application development.\nAndroid Studio was announced on May 16, 2013 at the Google I/O conference. It was in early access preview stage starting from version 0.1 in May 2013, then entered beta stage starting from version 0.8 which was released in June 2014.[11] The first stable build was released in December 2014, starting from version 1.0.[12]\nSince May 7, 2019, Kotlin is Google’s preferred language for Android app development.[13] Still, other programming languages are supported by Android Studio, such as Java and C++.</string>

    <string name="passage_two">Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android is developed by a consortium of developers known as the Open Handset Alliance, with the main contributor and commercial marketer being Google.\nInitially developed by Android Inc., which Google bought in 2005, Android was unveiled in 2007, with the first commercial Android device launched in September 2008. The current stable version is Android 10, released on September 3, 2019. The core Android source code is known as Android Open Source Project (AOSP), which is primarily licensed under the Apache License. This has allowed variants of Android to be developed on a range of other electronics, such as game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and others, each with a specialized user interface. Some well known derivatives include Android TV for televisions and Wear OS for wearables, both developed by Google.\nAndroid\'s source code has been used as the basis of different ecosystems, most notably that of Google which is associated with a suite of proprietary software called Google Mobile Services (GMS),[11] that frequently comes pre-installed on said devices. This includes core apps such as Gmail, the digital distribution platform Google Play and associated Google Play Services development platform, and usually apps such as the Google Chrome web browser. These apps are licensed by manufacturers of Android devices certified under standards imposed by Google. Other competing Android ecosystems include Amazon.com\'s Fire OS, or LineageOS. Software distribution is generally offered through proprietary application stores like Google Play Store or Samsung Galaxy Store, or open source platforms like Aptoide or F-Droid, which utilize software packages in the APK format.\nAndroid has been the best-selling OS worldwide on smartphones since 2011 and on tablets since 2013. As of May 2017, it has over two billion monthly active users, the largest installed base of any operating system, and as of December 2018, the Google Play Store features over 2.6 million apps.</string>

    <string name="passage_three">Linux (/ˈlɪnəks/ (About this soundlisten) LIN-əks)[9][10] is a family of open source Unix-like operating systems based on the Linux kernel,[11] an operating system kernel first released on September 17, 1991, by Linus Torvalds.[12][13][14] Linux is typically packaged in a Linux distribution.\nDistributions include the Linux kernel and supporting system software and libraries, many of which are provided by the GNU Project. Many Linux distributions use the word "Linux" in their name, but the Free Software Foundation uses the name GNU/Linux to emphasize the importance of GNU software, causing some controversy.\nPopular Linux distributions[17][18][19] include Debian, Fedora, and Ubuntu. Commercial distributions include Red Hat Enterprise Linux and SUSE Linux Enterprise Server. Desktop Linux distributions include a windowing system such as X11 or Wayland, and a desktop environment such as GNOME or KDE Plasma. Distributions intended for servers may omit graphics altogether, or include a solution stack such as LAMP. Because Linux is freely redistributable, anyone may create a distribution for any purpose.\nLinux was originally developed for personal computers based on the Intel x86 architecture, but has since been ported to more platforms than any other operating system.[20] Linux is the leading operating system on servers and other big iron systems such as mainframe computers, and the only OS used on TOP500 supercomputers (since November 2017, having gradually eliminated all competitors).[21][22][23] It is used by around 2.3 percent of desktop computers.[24][25] The Chromebook, which runs the Linux kernel-based Chrome OS, dominates the US K–12 education market and represents nearly 20 percent of sub-$300 notebook sales in the US.\nLinux also runs on embedded systems, i.e. devices whose operating system is typically built into the firmware and is highly tailored to the system. This includes routers, automation controls, televisions,[27][28] digital video recorders, video game consoles, and smartwatches.[29] Many smartphones and tablet computers run Android and other Linux derivatives.[30] Because of the dominance of Android on smartphones, Linux has the largest installed base of all general-purpose operating systems.\nLinux is one of the most prominent examples of free and open-source software collaboration. The source code may be used, modified and distributed—commercially or non-commercially—by anyone under the terms of its respective licenses, such as the GNU General Public License.</string>
    <string name="scrolling_text_label">Scrolling Text</string>
</resources>
